[{"answer": "All in all, it's seems some time since we did a speck of honest pirating", "docId": "Pirates-of-the-Caribbean-Dead-Man_s-Chest.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Aye, shiny", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "More acquaintance than friend. How do you know him", "docId": "Pirates-of-the-Caribbean-Dead-Man_s-Chest.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "What mark did he leave on you", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Freedom.  my friend is a dying breed. The world is shrinking, the blank pages of the map filled in. my friend must find his place in the new world or perish. Not unlike you, Mister Turner. You and your fiance face the hangman's noose", "docId": "Pirates-of-the-Caribbean-Dead-Man_s-Chest.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "The Black Pearl", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Properly", "docId": "Pirates-of-the-Caribbean-Dead-Man_s-Chest.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "If it weren't for these bars I'd have you already", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "?Unloose the mooring lines", "docId": "Pirates-of-the-Caribbean-Dead-Man_s-Chest.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Well, how'd you get it back last time", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "What we need to do is make sail for Port Royal with all haste", "docId": "Pirates-of-the-Caribbean-Dead-Man_s-Chest.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "You want me to find this", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "my friend... I shall trade you the Compass, if you will help me... to find", "docId": "Pirates-of-the-Caribbean-Dead-Man_s-Chest.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "No.", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "What's all this? If you both fancy the dress, you'll just have to share, and wear it one after the other", "docId": "Pirates-of-the-Caribbean-Dead-Man_s-Chest.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Is it now? 'N' you", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I'll watch your back", "docId": "Pirates-of-the-Caribbean-Dead-Man_s-Chest.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Mind the boat", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "You. You have a touch of... destiny about", "docId": "Pirates-of-the-Caribbean-Dead-Man_s-Chest.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "You want to know", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "You have a debt to pay. You've been captain of the Black Pearl for thirteen years.", "docId": "Pirates-of-the-Caribbean-Dead-Man_s-Chest.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Then you were a poor captain, but a", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Then you were a poor captain, but a", "docId": "Pirates-of-the-Caribbean-Dead-Man_s-Chest.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "One soul is not equal to another", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "You", "docId": "Pirates-of-the-Caribbean-Dead-Man_s-Chest.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Are you certain? Is that what you really want most", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "No! Don't do this", "docId": "Pirates-of-the-Caribbean-Dead-Man_s-Chest.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Four fives", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "It's a curious thing. There was a time when I would've given anything for you to look like that while thinking about me", "docId": "Pirates-of-the-Caribbean-Dead-Man_s-Chest.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Oh, I think you do", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I don't know what you mean", "docId": "Pirates-of-the-Caribbean-Dead-Man_s-Chest.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Oh, don't be absurd. I trust him, that's all", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "One word lov", "docId": "Pirates-of-the-Caribbean-Dead-Man_s-Chest.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Uh my Compass works fine", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Do tell, dearie", "docId": "Pirates-of-the-Caribbean-Dead-Man_s-Chest.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Not so easy, is it", "docId": "Pirates-of-the-Caribbean-Dead-Man_s-Chest.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "You do", "qsentId": 38}]